<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Ginlistic</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Ginlistic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bombay Sapphire</title>
      <link>/bombay-sapphire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 09:49:03 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bombay-sapphire/</guid>
      <description>About the Tanqueray London Dry Gin Bombay Sapphire was first introduced in 1987 and has since become a popular gin brand worldwide. Bombay Sapphire is a London Dry Gin that is made using a unique blend of ten botanicals, including juniper berries, coriander, angelica root, lemon peel, and grains of paradise.
The recipe for Bombay Sapphire gin is based on a 1761 recipe developed by Thomas Dakin, who is considered to be one of the forefathers of English gin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Ginlistic</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About privacy This site is nearly cookieless (apart from the cookies needed to run it)
## If you are a distillery
Soon I&amp;rsquo;ll post contact details if you want your gin to be included here or if you want to send me better pictures. Even a bottle would be nice.
If you are a photographer This site use pictures found on Unsplash under the free license. If you are an unsplash photographer and you have your own website, drop me a line and I&amp;rsquo;ll link it if you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aviation American Gin</title>
      <link>/aviation-american-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aviation-american-gin/</guid>
      <description>About the Aviation American Gin Aviation American Gin is a brand of gin produced in Portland, Oregon, United States. It was first launched in 2006 and has since gained popularity, winning several awards and gaining a celebrity following, including actor Ryan Reynolds who became an owner and spokesperson for the brand in 2018.
The gin is made with a unique blend of botanicals, including juniper, cardamom, lavender, coriander, and anise. It is distilled in a traditional copper pot still and bottled at 42% ABV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beefeater London Dry Gin</title>
      <link>/beefeater-london-dry-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/beefeater-london-dry-gin/</guid>
      <description>About the Beefeater London Dry Gin Beefeater London Dry Gin is a classic gin that has been around since 1820. It is made in London and is considered to be a quintessential example of a London dry gin. Beefeater is made using a combination of 9 botanicals including juniper, angelica root, angelica seeds, coriander seeds, liquorice, almonds, orris root, Seville oranges, and lemon peel.
Beefeater is known for its balanced flavor, with a prominent juniper taste, as well as citrus notes from the Seville oranges and lemon peel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elephant Gin</title>
      <link>/elephant-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/elephant-gin/</guid>
      <description>About the Elephant Gin Elephant Gin is a premium handcrafted gin made in Germany using 14 botanicals, including rare African ingredients such as baobab, Buchu plant, and African wormwood. The name Elephant Gin was inspired by the founders&amp;rsquo; love for Africa and their desire to support African elephant conservation. A portion of the proceeds from every bottle sold goes to charities that work to protect elephants and their habitats in Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Empress 1908 Gin</title>
      <link>/empress-1908-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/empress-1908-gin/</guid>
      <description>About the Empress 1908 Gin Empress 1908 Gin is a Canadian gin that is named after the Fairmont Empress Hotel in Victoria, British Columbia. The gin is known for its distinctive purple color, which comes from the infusion of butterfly pea flower petals during the distillation process. In addition to the butterfly pea flower, the gin is also made with eight other botanicals, including juniper, coriander, grapefruit peel, ginger root, and rose petal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gin Mare Mediterranean Gin</title>
      <link>/gin-mare-mediterranean-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gin-mare-mediterranean-gin/</guid>
      <description>About the Gin Mare Mediterranean Gin Gin Mare is a premium gin that is distilled in a small fishing village on the Mediterranean coast of Spain. It is known for its unique flavor profile that incorporates botanicals that are common in the Mediterranean region. The name &amp;ldquo;Mare&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;sea&amp;rdquo; in Italian, which reflects the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on the flavors and culture of the Mediterranean.
Gin Mare is made using a blend of nine different botanicals, including juniper berries, coriander seeds, cardamom, and citrus peels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greater Than London Dry Gin</title>
      <link>/greater-than-london-dry-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/greater-than-london-dry-gin/</guid>
      <description>Greater Than London Dry Gin is made with 9 botanicals, including juniper berries, coriander seeds, angelica root, orris root, lemon peel, orange peel, licorice, fennel, and chamomile. The gin is made in small batches using a copper pot still, and the botanicals are steeped in a neutral spirit for 24 hours before distillation.
The resulting gin has a crisp and citrusy flavor profile, with notes of juniper, lemon, and coriander. It is smooth and well-balanced, with a clean and refreshing finish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hapusa Gin</title>
      <link>/hapusa-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hapusa-gin/</guid>
      <description>Hapusa Gin is an artisanal gin produced in India by the Nao Spirits &amp;amp; Beverages company. It is a premium quality gin that is inspired by the unique botanicals found in the Himalayan region of India. Here are some of the key features and characteristics of Hapusa Gin:
Botanicals: Hapusa Gin is made using a blend of 12 botanicals, six of which are native to the Himalayas. These include juniper, coriander seeds, turmeric, mango ginger, cardamom, and gondhoraj limes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hendrick&#39;s</title>
      <link>/hendricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hendricks/</guid>
      <description>Hendrick&amp;rsquo;s Gin it&amp;rsquo;s a Scottish gin that has become increasingly popular in recent years. Hendrick&amp;rsquo;s Gin is known for its unique flavor profile, which is achieved through the use of a blend of eleven botanicals, including juniper, coriander, and citrus peel, as well as more unusual ingredients such as cucumber and rose petals.
Hendrick&amp;rsquo;s Gin is distilled using a small-batch method that involves the use of both a copper pot still and a rare Carter-Head still, which helps to preserve the delicate flavors of the botanicals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hendrick&#39;s Lunar Gin</title>
      <link>/hendricks-lunar-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hendricks-lunar-gin/</guid>
      <description>Hendrick&amp;rsquo;s Lunar Gin is a limited edition release from Hendrick&amp;rsquo;s Gin, a Scottish distillery known for its unique and unconventional approach to gin-making. It was inspired by the mysterious and ephemeral qualities of the moon and is intended to be a sippable and contemplative gin for moments of calm and introspection.
The gin is distilled with a selection of botanicals including juniper, coriander, angelica root, orris root, and orange peel, as well as more unusual ingredients like lemon verbena, silver birch, and moonflower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jaisalmer Indian Craft Gin</title>
      <link>/jaisalmer-indian-craft-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jaisalmer-indian-craft-gin/</guid>
      <description>Jaisalmer Indian Craft Gin is a premium gin produced by Radico Khaitan, a well-known Indian distillery that has been in operation since 1943. The gin is named after the Jaisalmer Fort, a historic landmark in the Indian state of Rajasthan.
Jaisalmer Indian Craft Gin is made with a blend of 11 botanicals, including juniper berries, coriander seeds, lemon peel, and cubeb berries, which are all sourced from around the world. In addition to these traditional gin botanicals, the recipe also includes Indian botanicals such as darjeeling tea and lemongrass, giving the gin a unique flavor profile that is both familiar and exotic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monkey 47</title>
      <link>/monkey-47/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/monkey-47/</guid>
      <description>Monkey 47 is a premium gin that is made in the Black Forest region of Germany. It is a complex and nuanced gin that is made with 47 different botanicals, including juniper, lavender, and lingonberries, among others. The gin is distilled in small batches using a combination of traditional maceration and vapor infusion techniques, which allows the flavors of the botanicals to develop in a gentle and controlled way. With a relatively high alcohol content of 47%, Monkey 47 is a gin that is designed for gin enthusiasts who appreciate the complex and layered flavors that a premium gin can offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nikka Coffey Gin</title>
      <link>/nikka-coffey-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nikka-coffey-gin/</guid>
      <description>Nikka Coffey Gin is a premium Japanese gin produced by Nikka Whisky Distilling Company, which is known for its award-winning whiskies. The gin is made using a unique Coffey still, which was originally designed by Aeneas Coffey in the 19th century, and is rarely used for gin production. This still allows the distillers to create a high-quality spirit with a silky texture and a depth of flavor.
The botanicals used in Nikka Coffey Gin are sourced from all over Japan, including yuzu from the north, sansho pepper from the central area, and kabosu and amanatsu from the south.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roku Gin</title>
      <link>/roku-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/roku-gin/</guid>
      <description>Roku Gin is a premium Japanese gin that is produced by the House of Suntory. The name &amp;ldquo;roku&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;six&amp;rdquo; in Japanese, and this gin gets its name from the six traditional Japanese botanicals used to craft it. In addition to these six botanicals, Roku Gin also includes eight other traditional gin botanicals, resulting in a complex and balanced flavor profile.
The six traditional Japanese botanicals used in Roku Gin include sakura flower, sakura leaf, yuzu peel, sencha tea, gyokuro tea, and sansho pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sipsmith London Dry Gin</title>
      <link>/sipsmith-london-dry-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sipsmith-london-dry-gin/</guid>
      <description>Sipsmith London Dry Gin is a classic gin from the renowned Sipsmith Distillery in London, UK. It is crafted using traditional methods and only the finest ingredients, including Macedonian juniper berries, coriander seeds, angelica root, liquorice root, orris root, and lemon peel.
The botanicals are steeped in a copper pot still overnight and then distilled in small batches, resulting in a smooth and well-balanced gin with a classic London Dry style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stranger &amp; Sons Gin</title>
      <link>/stranger-sons-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stranger-sons-gin/</guid>
      <description>Stranger &amp;amp; Sons is a premium gin brand that hails from India. It is made using a variety of locally sourced botanicals, as well as traditional gin ingredients such as juniper berries, coriander seeds, and angelica root. One of the standout ingredients in Stranger &amp;amp; Sons Gin is the addition of Himalayan juniper berries, which give the gin a distinctively spicy and earthy flavor profile.
Other botanicals used in Stranger &amp;amp; Sons Gin include licorice root, nutmeg, cassia bark, and citrus peels, which add a complex and aromatic quality to the spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanqueray London Dry Gin</title>
      <link>/tanqueray-london-dry-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tanqueray-london-dry-gin/</guid>
      <description>About the Tanqueray distillery Tanqueray was first produced in England in the 1830s and has since become a popular gin worldwide. Its distinctive taste is attributed to a unique blend of botanicals, including juniper, coriander, angelica root, and liquorice. In addition to its classic London Dry Gin, Tanqueray also produces a range of other gins, including Tanqueray No. Ten, which is made with fresh citrus fruits, and Tanqueray Rangpur, which is distilled with Rangpur limes for a citrusy twist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Botanist Islay Dry Gin</title>
      <link>/the-botanist-islay-dry-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-botanist-islay-dry-gin/</guid>
      <description>The Botanist Islay Dry Gin is a premium gin produced by the Bruichladdich Distillery, which is best known for its whisky production. This gin is made from 22 hand-foraged botanicals from the island of Islay, Scotland, including wild Islay juniper, apple mint, chamomile, heather, and thistle, as well as a few other secret ingredients.
The gin is distilled in a unique Lomond still, which was originally designed to produce whisky but has been adapted for gin production.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
