<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>England on Ginlistic</title>
    <link>/categories/england/</link>
    <description>Recent content in England on Ginlistic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 09:49:03 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/england/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bombay Sapphire</title>
      <link>/bombay-sapphire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 09:49:03 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bombay-sapphire/</guid>
      <description>About the Tanqueray London Dry Gin Bombay Sapphire was first introduced in 1987 and has since become a popular gin brand worldwide. Bombay Sapphire is a London Dry Gin that is made using a unique blend of ten botanicals, including juniper berries, coriander, angelica root, lemon peel, and grains of paradise.
The recipe for Bombay Sapphire gin is based on a 1761 recipe developed by Thomas Dakin, who is considered to be one of the forefathers of English gin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beefeater London Dry Gin</title>
      <link>/beefeater-london-dry-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/beefeater-london-dry-gin/</guid>
      <description>About the Beefeater London Dry Gin Beefeater London Dry Gin is a classic gin that has been around since 1820. It is made in London and is considered to be a quintessential example of a London dry gin. Beefeater is made using a combination of 9 botanicals including juniper, angelica root, angelica seeds, coriander seeds, liquorice, almonds, orris root, Seville oranges, and lemon peel.
Beefeater is known for its balanced flavor, with a prominent juniper taste, as well as citrus notes from the Seville oranges and lemon peel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boodles Gin</title>
      <link>/boodles-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/boodles-gin/</guid>
      <description>Boodles Gin is a London dry gin that was first produced in the mid-19th century in the UK. The gin is named after Boodle&amp;rsquo;s gentleman&amp;rsquo;s club in London, which was a popular hangout for aristocrats and politicians in the 18th and 19th centuries. Boodles Gin is made with a unique blend of botanicals, including juniper, coriander seed, angelica root, cassia bark, and nutmeg, among others. It is a relatively light gin with a smooth, clean taste and a subtle spiciness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sipsmith London Dry Gin</title>
      <link>/sipsmith-london-dry-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sipsmith-london-dry-gin/</guid>
      <description>Sipsmith London Dry Gin is a classic gin from the renowned Sipsmith Distillery in London, UK. It is crafted using traditional methods and only the finest ingredients, including Macedonian juniper berries, coriander seeds, angelica root, liquorice root, orris root, and lemon peel.
The botanicals are steeped in a copper pot still overnight and then distilled in small batches, resulting in a smooth and well-balanced gin with a classic London Dry style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanqueray London Dry Gin</title>
      <link>/tanqueray-london-dry-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tanqueray-london-dry-gin/</guid>
      <description>About the Tanqueray distillery Tanqueray was first produced in England in the 1830s and has since become a popular gin worldwide. Its distinctive taste is attributed to a unique blend of botanicals, including juniper, coriander, angelica root, and liquorice. In addition to its classic London Dry Gin, Tanqueray also produces a range of other gins, including Tanqueray No. Ten, which is made with fresh citrus fruits, and Tanqueray Rangpur, which is distilled with Rangpur limes for a citrusy twist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
