<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>London Dry Gin on Ginlistic</title>
    <link>/categories/london-dry-gin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in London Dry Gin on Ginlistic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 09:49:03 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/london-dry-gin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bombay Sapphire</title>
      <link>/bombay-sapphire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 09:49:03 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bombay-sapphire/</guid>
      <description>About the Tanqueray London Dry Gin Bombay Sapphire was first introduced in 1987 and has since become a popular gin brand worldwide. Bombay Sapphire is a London Dry Gin that is made using a unique blend of ten botanicals, including juniper berries, coriander, angelica root, lemon peel, and grains of paradise.
The recipe for Bombay Sapphire gin is based on a 1761 recipe developed by Thomas Dakin, who is considered to be one of the forefathers of English gin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beefeater London Dry Gin</title>
      <link>/beefeater-london-dry-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/beefeater-london-dry-gin/</guid>
      <description>About the Beefeater London Dry Gin Beefeater London Dry Gin is a classic gin that has been around since 1820. It is made in London and is considered to be a quintessential example of a London dry gin. Beefeater is made using a combination of 9 botanicals including juniper, angelica root, angelica seeds, coriander seeds, liquorice, almonds, orris root, Seville oranges, and lemon peel.
Beefeater is known for its balanced flavor, with a prominent juniper taste, as well as citrus notes from the Seville oranges and lemon peel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greater Than London Dry Gin</title>
      <link>/greater-than-london-dry-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/greater-than-london-dry-gin/</guid>
      <description>Greater Than London Dry Gin is made with 9 botanicals, including juniper berries, coriander seeds, angelica root, orris root, lemon peel, orange peel, licorice, fennel, and chamomile. The gin is made in small batches using a copper pot still, and the botanicals are steeped in a neutral spirit for 24 hours before distillation.
The resulting gin has a crisp and citrusy flavor profile, with notes of juniper, lemon, and coriander. It is smooth and well-balanced, with a clean and refreshing finish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanqueray London Dry Gin</title>
      <link>/tanqueray-london-dry-gin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tanqueray-london-dry-gin/</guid>
      <description>About the Tanqueray distillery Tanqueray was first produced in England in the 1830s and has since become a popular gin worldwide. Its distinctive taste is attributed to a unique blend of botanicals, including juniper, coriander, angelica root, and liquorice. In addition to its classic London Dry Gin, Tanqueray also produces a range of other gins, including Tanqueray No. Ten, which is made with fresh citrus fruits, and Tanqueray Rangpur, which is distilled with Rangpur limes for a citrusy twist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
